Do it
[music]
Press this button to subscribe to Information Technology Center
Welcome friends
welcome back to my channel Information Technology Center
If you are on the channel for the first time then
check the playlist of the channel there best
investment plan money
Today I have some useful news for you news a bit
old news but the
landmark decision of the Supreme Court on accidents
or the
insurance companies should take action against motor accidents at all costs If there is an accident
on the road then the
amount which is
appointed by the Supreme Court in small way The Supreme Court has given the
claim of the victims of road accidents the right to future prospects
whether the victim or the deceased has any
regular income or not means the
Supreme Court has said that the person who dies may
or may not have any income
but if he has met with an accident then
he should be given compensation for the accident now how about
here a division bench of two judges of the Supreme Court
said in its decision that the
legal heirs of the person who had no one at the time of his death,
except for future growth,
meaning for future prospects a student is doing this while studying that
after his death his parents become his
nominee or as if he has got married
So his wife would be his mother in law, so in this,
when that person was not earning anything, then
how will his tea related claim be made, firstly, in the claim, it is seen
what that person is doing and
in the future, both the persons are not doing anything in the future,
but
regarding the future, then the
bench of Justice Shah and Justice Sanjiv Khanna
said that it is not expected that
if the deceased was not in any job, there will be no possibility of his regular employment, it does
not matter, if someone is helpless, a
student, a working professional, a government
employee or a private employee,
even the Home Minister, if he has met with a
motor accident, then he will be given compensation amount.
Now this thing was
rejected by the Union Bank of India, the argument that at the
time when the deceased was not in a job, the future prospects
of growth and nothing else should be added, in
which the Union of India had said that
he was not a student, hence on the
basis of possibility of economic growth,
where is the motor accident, okay,
and they had said that therefore, instead of Rs. 12 lakh, we should just
claim it, he has
no income, hence there is no possibility of increase in income that
he will be able to earn in the future.  The calculation of how much it will
increase cannot be done,
therefore, we will only cover those who are primarily ill in motor accidents. The
insurance amount will not be given on the basis of their growth.
Then what happens is that their age has to be determined on the
basis of estimation considering the circumstances.
In this case, the court
ruled that if a person who is
currently earning and is
not doing anything, then his future condition should be
determined considering his condition and the
additional amount on future increase should be
calculated, that is, if an engineering student earns Rs.
10,000 in the future,
then at least his salary will be Rs. 10,000
and then as long as his salary increases by
3% every year, then it should be
given to him on an increasing amount accordingly.
His family
cannot have any dispute on the fact that the
cost will increase
because
as the age increases, the
court accepted that from the date of filing of the petition
till the date of recovery he had not subscribed
and
then he will take it. In this case, the
Supreme Court said that you have no
hope on top of that because you delayed so much.
It cannot be said that the child was only
studying and hence he has no income,
hence there is a possibility of any shortage in the future
and for this reason, on the basis of his growth,
any person is appointed to him at one and a half,
along with it,
how much income of that person is there at that
time or not,
his current income is seen,
in the form of estimation or in actual form, after seeing it, the
possibility of his growth is seen
and then by combining these two, the
Supreme Court has given this decision that the
insurance companies should pay the
compensation
amount of motor accident at all costs and in what form, the
person who is killed in a road accident, whether he has income
or not, whether he earns or not
or a student or any
person of any type,
based on his ability in the future, the amount
of accident insurance is estimated and according to his growth,
you must have liked the video, if you liked the channel then do
subscribe and subscribe
to my channel,
subscribe to the channel, Masters Series, Computer
Mobile Solutions and Best Investment
Plans, you will get 100% correct and complete information,
you must check the playlist on my time,
there you will see all these investment
plans where your money will be invested  It will be made
and the child's too. Thank you very much for watching today's entire video.